<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>scienxlab</title>
<link>https://scienxlab.org/blog.html</link>
<atom:link href="https://scienxlab.org/blog.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description></description>
<generator>quarto-1.3.450</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>Welcome to scienxlab</title>
  <dc:creator>Matt Hall</dc:creator>
  <link>https://scienxlab.org/blog/welcome-to-scienxlab.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p><strong>A lot has happened in the 413 days since <a href="https://agilescientific.com/blog/2022/8/29/a-machine-learning-safety-net">my last blog post</a>.</strong></p>
<p>With my colleagues, I shut down <a href="https://agilescientific.com">Agile</a> in September. With my family, I packed up my house in October and moved to Norway in November. With my new colleagues, I found my feet in <a href="https://equinor.com">Equinor</a> in December, and that adventure continues.</p>
<p>Having started my career as a geologist, then reconfigured as a geophysicist, I’m proud to call myself <em>a developer</em> today. I still have tons to learn about maintaining large projects in an enterprise setting, but I do make things and I consider that to be the killer feature of any hacker.</p>
<p>A few people have asked me what it’s like to have a boss again, or work inside a big corporation. But really, it’s not that different from working with corporate clients. I still have a lot of self-determination, thanks to the progressive style of the awesome team I work in, and the only thing I really miss is being able to decide for myself that I’d like to spend $10k on a hackathon.</p>
<p>Life outside work is full of hikes and bikes, far-flung fjords and cosy cabins. My Norwegian is a bit rusty (my wife and I lived here in the nineties) but basically functional. We found a house to live in, though it did require some downsizing.</p>
<p>In case you hadn’t noticed, this blog post is more of a postcard to the many friends and co-conspirators I’ve completely failed to keep in touch with. With luck, the coming months and years will provide many opportunities to catch up in person.</p>
<p><strong>For now though… the blog is back! Scien✖️lab is here 🚀</strong></p>



 ]]></description>
  <guid>https://scienxlab.org/blog/welcome-to-scienxlab.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
